sierratradingpost.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - We Are All Explorers.

This policy will be effective starting February 11, 2013

Welcome to **sierratradingpost.com** (the "Website"), the website for **Sierra Trading Post, Inc.** , a division of The TJX Companies, Inc. ("TJX"). TJX, Sierra Trading Post, Derailed, T.J. Maxx, Marshalls, HomeGoods, and other affiliates are the "TJX Businesses." This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect about our customers on our Website, in our stores, through our mobile applications, and through interest-based online advertising. The Privacy Notice also describes how we may use that information, how we protect that information, how we share that information, your choices and options regarding the information, and how you can contact us regarding our privacy practices.

## Information We Collect

We may collect certain personal information from you in connection with your activities at Sierra Trading Post, such as when you shop on our Website, through our catalogs, in our stores, or on our mobile applications. This information may include: 

  * Payment card or other financial account information; 
  * contact and billing information (including name, e-mail address, postal address, and phone number); 
  * driver's license number, military identification or state-issued picture identification;
  * date of birth; 
  * geolocation data; and
  * other personal information you provide to us on our Website, through our catalogs, in our stores, on our mobile applications, or when you interact with us in other ways, both online and offline. 

Additionally, we or companies acting on our behalf may collect certain computer and browser information through automated technologies such as cookies and web beacons when you visit our Website or download or use one of our mobile applications. A "cookie" is a file that a website sends to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to identify the browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. 

The information collected using these tools may include your IP address, browser characteristics, operating system, the address of the web page that referred you to our Website, dates and times of Website visits, the language your system uses, and the country and time zone in which your device is located. These automated technologies also permit the collection of "clickstream data," which may include a log of content you access while browsing a website. 

Companies acting on our behalf may combine the information collected from your visit to our Website with other information they have collected previously. Your web browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict, reject or disable certain cookies. 

## Interest-Based Online Advertising and Google Analytics

This section of our Privacy Notice provides details about interest-based online advertising (also called "targeted advertising", “remarketing”, or "behavioral advertising"), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.

We use Google Analytics’ 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to better understanding the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on this website or other websites because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies and web beacons). These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. Because those opt-out and preference control pages are specific to the individual browser used to visit it, and because that page is not operated by the TJX Businesses, we are unable to perform the opt-outs on your behalf.

## How We Use the Information We Collect

When we collect information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Process, manage, complete and account for transactions, including purchases and refund, exchange and layaway requests; 
  * Provide our products and services to you and fulfill your gift card orders; 
  * Identify your product and service preferences; 
  * Improve merchandise selections and customer service; 
  * Invite you to participate in customer research; 
  * Notify you about new products, services, features, promotions, events and special offerings relating to the TJX Businesses we think you will find valuable; 
  * Provide customer support and respond to your requests, comments and inquiries;
  * Create and manage online accounts you establish;
  * Enroll you in and administer our loyalty and other rewards programs upon your request;
  * Administer your participation in promotions, contests and sweepstakes;
  * Verify your identity in certain instances (such as when you pay by check, return merchandise, or request a refund); 
  * Protect against, identify and help prevent fraud, unauthorized activity, claims and other liabilities and minimize credit risk; 
  * Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, our policies, and our Terms of Use; and
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services, managing our communications, performing market research, and administering our Website).

We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

In addition, we use information collected online through automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users' visits to our Website and mobile applications; (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users' interests and the manner in which our users browse our Website and mobile applications; (iii) measuring and managing the advertising effectiveness of our online and offline advertisements and events; and (iv) managing our business. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our Website and mobile applications, identify users of our Website and mobile applications, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our websites, how users navigate through our websites, and how we may tailor our websites to better meet the needs of our users. In order for us to maintain the accuracy of your personal information and improve our communication with you, we may also supplement the information we collect with other public demographic information.

## Information We Share

We may share your personal information among the TJX Businesses (which are affiliates owned by TJX, including Derailed, T.J. Maxx, Marshalls, HomeGoods, Winners, HomeSense, and T.K. Maxx). They may use this information to offer products and services to you consistent with the purposes identified in this statement. Your information may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation) involving all or part of the TJX Businesses or as part of a stock sale or other change in corporate control.

We may share your name and mailing address with other businesses if you are on our paper-catalogue mailing list, unless you have requested that we not share this information. You may ask us not to share your name and address from our mailing list with these businesses, or ask to be removed from our catalogue mailing list, by contacting us as specified in the "Contact Information" section.

If a contest, sweepstakes or promotion is jointly-sponsored by us and one or more other sponsors, your information may be shared with such sponsors. We do not control other sponsors' use of your personal information, and their use of your information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to participate in such jointly sponsored contests, sweepstakes or promotions. Such offerings may also be subject to additional rules and regulations governing your participation.

We may also share certain personal information we collect about you with partners or third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. For example, we may use third parties to host our Website, operate certain of its features, send e-mails, print or send mailings, run our sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, conduct customer research, authorize and process your payments, manage and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness, and fulfill gift card orders. Such third-party service providers are given the information that they need to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own or any others' marketing purposes.

We also may share the information you provide (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) with law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

## Children's Privacy

We do not seek nor will we knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.

## Links

Our Website may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These linked websites operate independently from TJX and may have their own privacy notices or policies. Other linked websites may be owned or controlled by TJX but have privacy policies that differ from this one. To the extent any linked websites you visit are not owned or controlled by TJX, we are not responsible for the websites' content, any use of the websites, or the privacy practices of the websites. We suggest you review the privacy policies of any linked websites you visit.

## How We Protect Your Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your personal information.

## Your Options

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit a request, you may contact us as described in the Contact Information section.

You can opt out of receiving promotional e-mail and/or postal mail from us by doing the following: 

  * If you originally signed up for Sierra Trading Post e-mail, you can opt out from that e-mail by going to this page: <http://www.sierratradingpost.com/dealflyer/dffrequency/>. You then must enter your e-mail address, select the "Unsubscribe" option, and **click the "Save Changes" button**. Please be sure to enter the same e-mail address you provided when you signed up, otherwise it may not be possible to comply with your request.
  * If you have received an e-mail from Sierra Trading Post, you can opt out from receiving further e-mails by **following the opt-out or "unsubscribe" instructions provided in the e-mail you received**.
  * If you have an online account, you can login and manage your subscription preferences in My Account.
  * Contact us if you do not want to receive promotional e-mail and/or postal mail communications from us in the future. Please specify if you would like to opt out of e-mail, or postal mail, or both. If you have already received communications from us, it will expedite the opt-out process if you are prepared to provide us with the exact name, and e-mail and/or postal mail addresses under which you have been receiving communications from us.

Please note that any opt-out for postal mail may take at least sixty (60) days to become effective. Also, you may still receive e-mail or postal mail from other members of the TJX Businesses if they received your e-mail or postal address from other sources or as a result of their own transactions or experiences with you, or if you request to hear from us again.

As described in the "Interest-Based Online Advertising" section, you may learn more about how to opt out of ad network interest-based advertising by visiting the [consumer opt-out page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Consistent with the choices available in the "Information We Share" section, you also may withdraw your consent or object to certain information sharing by contacting us as indicated below. 

## Your Account

  * Sierra Trading Post reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, and/or cancel orders in its sole discretion.
  * Sierra Trading Post reserves the right to address accounts with abnormally high return rates.
  * Sierra Trading Post reserves the right to address accounts returning high amounts of used/worn merchandise.

## Notice to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California law provides that you be given the opportunity to opt out of our sharing your personal information with third parties that would use such personal information for their own direct marketing. Absent such an opt-out, we may share your information with other TJX Businesses (which are affiliates owned by TJX, including Derailed, T.J. Maxx, Marshalls and HomeGoods), to provide you with information about their products, services or promotions that we think may be of interest to you. We also may share your information with other non-affiliates absent such an opt-out, as described in the "Information We Share" section above. Accordingly, per California law, we provide a way for you to opt out if you do not want us to share your information in this manner.

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information with certain of our affiliates and other third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting Customer Service. If you have already received communications from us, it will expedite the opt-out process if you are prepared to provide us with the exact name, e-mail and/or postal mail addresses under which you have been receiving communications from us. Please note that it may take us up to 30 days to fully process your opt-out request. 

To review our complete Privacy Notice, please [click here](http://www.sierratradingpost.com/lp2/privacy-policy/).

## Contact Information

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Notice, or if you wish to update the personal information you have provided to us, you may contact customer service.

## Changes to Our Notice

This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices. We will post a prominent notice on the site to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice and indicate when it was most recently updated.
